asianet.co.in 2013-06-09

# Welcome to Asianet Satellite Communications Ltd.

asianet.co.in is sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet and is committed to safeguarding the privacy of user online.  

asianet.co.in collects personally identifiable data such as names, addresses and e-mail addresses that are voluntarily submitted by a user when he/she wishes to become a registered user of the services provided.

Personal information collected is used in the following manner. One of the reasons to collect information from users registering on asianet.co.in is to customise the services at asianet.co.in. The more information the user volunteers the better the experience on asianet.co.in  

asianet.co.in would also use cookies to customise the services provided to the user. These are small amounts of data that are sent to the user's browser from the web server and stored in the user's hard disk. You are required to accept cookies wherever you are prompted to login. These are basically Zip codes that categorise the user based on interests and behaviour.  

Personal information is used to deliver targeted advertisements to the user according to the specifications of the advertiser. This does not imply that the advertiser or any third party has an access to user's personal information. They will only receive aggregated user statistics (e.g. 60 % of our users are professionals.. Only asianet.co.in has access to Users' accounts.  

asianet.co.in will notify users prior to sharing the information collected with a partner of asianet.co.in or a sponsor of an event. You could choose not to allow that transfer by not using the service or by not participating in that particular event.   

Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personal information on chat areas, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other parties.  

asianet.co.in shall not reveal any personal information that users provide to us, to any third party without the users' permission, unless, asianet.co.in has a reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Use, or may be causing injury to, or interfering with the rights or property of itself, other users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. asianet.co.in may disclose or access account information when it believes in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service and improve our products and services.   

asianet.co.in is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by advertisers or sites to which links are provided by asianet.co.in 

Information provided by all Users needs to be true, accurate, current and complete as required by the registration form and promptly updated to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. The privacy policy covers exchanges of personally identifiable information within sites of asianet.co.in.
